我是魯索，請留言
This is Russo. Please leave a message.
他不回我電話
He's not answering my calls.
玩完了，他一定知道
It's over, and he must know it.
你不認為他能夠重新振作？
You don't think  there's any way he can recover?
從現在起到11月5日  共和黨會在每個電台和電視台
The Republicans will play that interview  on every radio and television station
播放專訪
from now until November 5th.
我很同情那年輕人  不過我一開始就有疑慮
I sympathize with the kid,  but this was my concern from the beginning.
長官，我應該聽你的話
And I should've listened to you, sir.
我以為他可以耐住壓力
I thought he could handle the pressure.
所以他退出，我們得找人替代
Okay. So he withdraws.  We need to replace him.
有任何建議嗎？
You have any ideas?
只剩不到兩個月的時間？
With less than two months to go?
如果總統沒有  在早先的討論把我剔除
If the President hadn't  shut me out of the early discussions,
我早就想出一些不錯的人選
I could've come up with some good options,
我真不知道誰既有知名度  又有獻金基礎
but I don't know anyone who's got  the name recognition and donor base
能在七周時間內  開始準備競選
to start a campaign  from scratch just seven weeks out.
讓我來想想
Let me think.
船到橋頭自然直
Everything hinges on the next few minutes.
我好幾個月的計劃  採取的行動，都是這樣來的
All my months of planning,  every move I've made.
- 有個人選  - 誰？
-There is one person.  -Who?
就是你，副總統
You, Mr. Vice President.
如果你再次競選  應該可以大勝
If you ran to reclaim your seat,  I think you'd win by a landslide.
要辭去副總統一職？
Resign the Vice Presidency?
只有你贏才能如此
Only ifyou win.
沃克需要我搭檔競選2016年
Walker needs me for 2016.
你確定他會邀你搭檔？
Are you entirely certain  he's gonna keep you on the ticket?
你們兩個不太合
I mean, it's no secret
這不是什麼秘密
the two of you don't exactly get along.
他說了什麼？
What has he said?
副總統，你讓我很為難
Oh, you're putting me in a very  awkward position, Mr. Vice President.
他說我壞話？
Has he been bad-mouthing me?
他說「很難搞」
Well, the exact phrase  he used was "pain in the ass."
渾蛋
That fucker.
他根本不知領導為何物  不懂得尊重
He's got no idea how to lead,  no sense of respect.
- 是他的意思？  - 不
-ls this his idea?  -No.
- 他要擺脫我？  - 我昨天才想到
-His way of getting rid of me?  -No. It struck me yesterday,
覺得可以提出來建議
and I just thought it was worth suggesting.
不過我還沒和任何人討論過
But, no, I haven't  discussed this with anyone.
你是不該討論  民眾也不允許副總統變成州長
And you shouldn't. People don't leave  the White House to become a governor.
長官，能否請教一個私人問題？
May I ask you a personal question, sir?
你想當副總統嗎？
Do you want to be the Vice President?
彼得說你投入那場競選時
Peter said that when you were  out on that campaign trail,
你非常熱心又活力十足
you had so much enthusiasm and energy
他覺得你可能  很想念當州長的日子
that he thought you maybe  missed being the Governor.
我是很想念
I do miss it.
你何不回去？
Then why not go back?
你會在這場選舉裏成為英雄
You could be the hero of this election
同時在2016年為民主黨  在賓州保住一席
and secure Pennsylvania  for the Democrats in 2016.
就算葛瑞很討厭我
Garrett would never go  along with something like this,
他絕不會做這樣的事
even if he hates my guts.
這會讓他顯得很弱  像是他無法掌控管理團隊
It would make him look weak,  like he's lost control of the administration.
如果是雙方的決定  就不會如此
Not if it was a mutual decision.
我來跟葛瑞談  我不會跟他說我們談過
Look, let me talk to Garrett.  I won't mention that we've spoken.
瞭解他的想法  應該不會有什麼問題
I suppose there's no harm in  finding out what he thinks.
副總統，謝謝
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
- 賞金四百元的標語  - 1976年「他讓我們再度驕傲」
-Slogans for $400.  -1976. "He's making us proud again. "
- 艾傑  - 誰是卡特？
-A.J.  -Who is Carter?
- 約翰是誰？  - 誰是福特？
-No. John?  -Who's Ford?
彼得？
Peter?
賞金六百元的標語
Slogans for $600.
彼得，你在嗎？
Peter, are you here?
「班足以勝任總統」
"Grandfather's hat fits Ben. "
- 克勞蒂亞  - 班傑明哈里森是誰？
-Claudia.  -Who is Benjamin Harrison?
- 對  - 賞金八百元的總統競選標語
-Yes.  -Presidential Slogans for $800.
1900年「完美服務」
1900. "The full dinner pail. "
我搭火車時，差點報警  要他們破門而入
On the train ride down, I almost  called the police to have them break in
確定你沒有自殘
and make sure you hadn't hurt yourself.
我不會問你發生什麼事  現在這不重要
I'm not even gonna ask you what happened.  It doesn't matter right now.
現在重要的是…
What matters right now...
- 重要的是…  - 誰是戈德華特？
-What matters...  -Who is Goldwater?
- 克勞蒂亞  - 誰是戈德華特？
-Claudia.  -Who is Goldwater?
巴利戈德華特
Barry Goldwater. Yes.
- 銳利如刀，賞金八百元  - 正式方式…
-Cuts Like a Knife for $800.  -The official instrument...
別這樣，我正在看
Oh, come on. Hey, I'm watching that.
重要的是你屋前的50名記者
What matters is the 50 reporters  in front of your building
還有150名不知道自己是否  還有工作的競選工作人員
and the 150 campaign staffers  who don't know if they still have a job.
玩完了
It's over.
我知道
I know.
叫他們離開
So, tell them to go away.
你打算躲在這裏  希望事情自行落幕？
What, are you just gonna hole yourself  up in here and hope it all goes away?
我就是這麼打算
Yeah, that's pretty much the plan.
我不允許
Well, I won't let you.
放下
Hey, put that down. Hey.
- 放下！  - 彼得…
-Hey, put that down!  -Peter...
我們得發表聲明
We need to put out a statement.
你準備好時打電話給我
Call me when you're prepared to do that.
我會在費城的總部
I'll be at the headquarters in Philly.
我怕愛上你
I was scared that I was starting to feel  too much for you.
所以才會結束
I think, that's why I ended it.
你不允許害怕嗎？
And you have no room for fear?
一害怕就成事不足
No. Being afraid  doesn't accomplish anything.
不對，我在國外時  合理的害怕疾病或暴力
It's not true. When I'm overseas,  rational fear of disease or violence,
這種害怕讓你得以生存
that sort of fear keeps you alive.
回到這裏，我發現自己
Back here, God, I find myself afraid of things
不知在怕什麼
that I can't name or point to.
那就是，我有多渺小？
It's like, how little am I seeing?
或我浪費了今天或當下？
Or have I wasted this day or this moment?
我有時會想  我的生命是否有價值
Yeah, I think that sometimes,  whether my life will add up.
法蘭斯要是聽到這樣的話  會覺得很蠢
Francis would roll his eyes  if he heard me talking like this.
他知道你在哪裏嗎？
Does he know where you are?
他不知道
No, he doesn't.
要是他找你，你應該在那裏
If he's looking for you, that's where you are.
在那邊
Over there.
在你遇到法蘭之前
Before you met Frank.
一個人
Alone.
生性好奇
Curious.
求知若渴
Absorbing everything.
你絕對想不到我年輕時的樣子
You have no idea  what I was like when I was a girl.
他知道你的那一面嗎？
Did he ever know that side ofyou?
他對於我的那一面沒興趣
He wasn't interested in that girl.
我也沒有
And neither was l.
你對什麼有興趣？
What were you interested in?
不只是個觀察者
Being more than an observer.
你希望被看見
You wanted to be seen.
不只被看見
Not just seen.
我想成為重要人物
I wanted to be significant.
沒有慣例可循
There's no historical precedent.
艾朗布爾競選州長  卡霍競選參議員
Aaron Burr ran for governor,  Calhoun for the Senate.
兩百年前，一個在槍戰殺死人  另一個支持蓄奴
Two hundred years ago. One shot a man  in a duel, the other believed in slavery.
法蘭，我們要跟他們一樣嗎？
Is that really the sort of  company we want to share, Frank?
總統，我們可能會輸掉  相當有影響力的一州
Mr. President, we stand losing  control of an important swing state,
眾議院多數和你的競選連任
our majority in the House, and quite  possibly your second term in office.
想要選贏得使出非常手段
Preventing all of that may  require unconventional measures.
這像是要除掉他
It would look like I'm pushing him out.
或更糟的辭職
Or worse,  that he's abandoning the administration.
你們一起發表聲明
You make a joint statement.
你宣佈除非他選贏  否則不會辭職
You say he won't resign unless he wins.
要是選輸了，他仍是副總統
If he loses, he stays on as Vice President.
沒有人會責怪你們  對彼此不忠誠
No one could accuse either of you  of disloyalty to the other.
- 吉姆跟你提這個想法？  - 完全是我想的
-Did Jim come to you with this?  -No. It's entirely my idea.
在跟副總統講之前  我一定要先跟你提才行
I wouldn't dream of speaking to the Vice  President without passing it by you first.
我想他會認為這是種侮辱
I think he'd take it as an affront,
像是我要趕走他
Iike I'm trying to get rid of him.
老實說，我想他會有興趣  超乎你想像
Honestly, sir, I think he might be  more interested than you imagine.
- 為什麼？  - 我不太想提
-Why is that?  -Well, I hesitate to bring this up,
不過當他為魯索競選時
but when he was campaigning for Russo,
他說了你不少事
he spoke quite freely about you, sir.
告訴我
Tell me.
當然我是從彼得那裏聽來的
Of course, I'm getting  this secondhand from Peter,
不過重點在…
but the gist of it is that...
你完全缺乏領導能力
That you lack entirely in leadership,
也不懂得尊重
and that you have no sense of respect.
他想要更多職責？
And he wants more responsibility?
他欠缺思慮、不守規矩  我如何賦予他重任？
And how do I give him that when he shows  absolutely no discretion, no discipline?
這就是我的重點  我完全負起支持魯索的責任
Well, that is entirely my point. Now, look,  I take full responsibility for backing Russo,
不過事情總會有轉機
but there could be a silver lining in all this.
你可以完成兩個目標
You could accomplish two goals.
為民主黨保住賓州
Secure Pennsylvania for the Democrats
同時找出顧及情面的方法  換掉馬修
and find an honorable  way to replace Matthews.
你認為呢？
What do you think?
這是很重大的決定  我們不想急就章
I think it is a very big decision,  and we do not want to make it impulsively.
同意，我想多做些考量
I agree.  I'd like to put some more thought into it.
長官，這麼做很審慎  請記住
Well, that is very prudent, sir.  Just bear in mind,
只有七周，每一天都很重要
seven weeks out, that every day counts.
- 先生  - 這個多少錢？
-Hi, sir.  -How much is it?
我這裏有你的收據
Oh, I got your receipt right here.
不，只有40元
No, no, no. It was just $40.
不要告訴別人，好嗎？
Yeah. Don't tell anyone, all right?
我絕不會透露房客的事
No. I never say anything about our tenants.
- 媒體仍在外頭？  - 對
-The press still outside?  -Yeah.
按照你的意思  我告訴他們你不在
I told them you weren't here, like you said.
他們大部分都離開  不過還有幾個沒走
Most of them left. There's still a few, though.
如果我要離開  有地方能不被看見嗎？
If I wanted to leave, is there a place  I could do it without being seen?
有，到車庫的防火電梯
Yeah. The freight elevator  down to the garage.
- 我可以幫你叫計程車…  - 謝謝，有需要我會讓你知道
-I could call you a cab or...  -All right. Thanks. I'll let you know.
魯索先生…
Mr. Russo...
先生，這不關我的事
Sir, it's none of my business,
不過我叔叔戒酒失敗過幾次
but my uncle,  he fell off the wagon a few times.
這時，他最想身邊有人陪
When he did, the best thing  for him was just not to be alone.
我不會收你的錢  我會分擔你的重擔
I'll give you this money back,  I'll take that bag offyour hands,
進來這裏，與你作伴…
come in here, keep you company...
非常感謝，如果我改變心意  會告知你
I appreciate it.  I'll let you know if I change my mind.
坐下
Sit down.
克萊兒在哪？
Where's Claire?
不在這裏
Not here.
這是什麼？收尾嗎？
So what is this, tying up loose ends?
我不亂做臆測  像你這樣的人，不容易瞭解
I wouldn't presume.  People like you can't be neatly tied up.
不過我想我們可能可以…
But I thought perhaps we could start...
很有品味
It's very tasteful.
她穿這件去慈善會
This is the dress she wore to the gala.
我相信
I believe so.
的確如此
It is.
我認得
I recognize it.
回去臥室
Go back into the bedroom.
我很訝異  你把她拍得如此清楚
I'm amazed how well you got her in focus.
該稱她什麼？
What should we call her?
為何要名字？
Why does she need a name?
我從不為無名氏拍照
I never photograph anyone  without knowing their name.
你不拍這種照片，但是我拍
You didn't take the photograph. I did.
我們該稱她為克萊兒
I think we should call her Claire.
她根本和我不像
She doesn't even look like me.
也不像年輕的我  你為什麼一直這樣說？
Not even a younger version.  Why do you keep saying that?
無關她的面貌、表情
Not her features, her expression.
我們應該把相片裱起來  你可以把她掛在你家
Hey, we should mount it.  You can hang her in your house.
法蘭斯會反對嗎？
Would Francis object?
可以不要討論法蘭斯嗎？
Can we please not discuss Francis?
是你在公園提起他
You brought him up in the park.
我知道，我不該如此
I know I did, and I shouldn't have.
所以我們得假裝他不存在？
So we have to pretend he doesn't exist?
我以為我們什麼都可以談
I thought we could talk about anything.
他是存在的，你必須承認
He is a presence here. You must admit that.
當你昨天走進門時
When you walked  through the door yesterday,
他馬上跟著你走進來
he walked right in with you.
只有我，沒有別人
It's just me, nobody else.
你一直這樣告訴自己  可能會成真
You keep telling yourself that,  it might come true.
如果她知道我穿這件  會怎麼想？
How do you think she'd feel  if she knew I was wearing this?
不知道
I don't know.
你覺得她會不高興嗎？
You don't think she'd be upset?
她可能會說你穿很漂亮
She'd probably say  you look very beautiful in it.
硬梆梆的
It's like steel.
你應該放回去
You should put it back.
我要留著
I think I'll keep it.
你要的話，我會買一件給你
I'll buy you one ofyour own, ifyou'd like.
不，我要這件
No. I want this one.
她去過我的臥房  應該知道我來過她的臥房
She came into my bedroom.  She should know I came into hers.
你的床鋪向來都這麼整齊嗎？
Is your bed always so perfectly made?
這是我念軍校時養成的習慣
It's a habit I formed at military school.
她睡哪一邊？
What side of the bed does she sleep on?
那邊
That side.
她可以留著
She can keep it.
更適合她
Fits her better anyway.
聽好，喬伊…
Listen, Zoe...
不管樓上發生什麼事  或是過去六個月的情形
Whatever just happened upstairs,  whatever these past six months have been,
我們能把事情單純化嗎？
can we agree that it is time to simplify?
單純化會是什麼樣子？
What does simple look like?
我們保持專業的安排
We maintain our professional arrangement,
如你建議，我會照辦
as you suggested, which I will honor.
你仍信任我？
You still trust me?
我還有其他選擇嗎？
What choice do I have?
你沒有像你說的傷害我  或棄我不顧
You didn't hurt me  or discard me like you said you would.
很高興我不必如此
I'm glad I didn't have to.
我們都同意要單純化
Yes, we'll agree to simplify.
好
Good.
法蘭，抱歉我來晚幾分鐘
Sorry I'm a few minutes late, Frank.
請坐
Please, have a seat.
我很清楚  你要求這次見面的原因
I have a pretty good idea why  you asked for this meeting.
你和總統談過了嗎？
Have you and the President  had a chance to speak?
談過了
We have.
- 他有偏向哪一方嗎？  - 他難以抉擇
-ls he leaning one way or another?  -He's torn.
- 你呢？  - 比他好一點
-And what about you?  -I'm a little less torn.
我的直覺告訴我，這樣不對
My instincts tell me it's a mistake.
你想說服我換個方式？
You want to convince me otherwise?
如果你的直覺認為  這樣行不通，我不打算…
Well, look, if your instincts tell you  this is not the way to go, I'm not about to...
法蘭，我要問你  兩個很直接的問題
Frank, I'm gonna ask you  two very direct questions,
也希望得到坦白的回答
and I would appreciate direct answers.
當你讓我兒子進大學
When you got my son into college,
有預期這樣的時刻嗎？
were you anticipating a moment like this?
不懂
I don't follow.
法蘭，請老實說？
Honestly, Frank?
我有預期…
Was I antici...
如果能瞭解你在問什麼  我很樂於據實以告
I would be happy to answer you  directly if I knew what you were asking.
我問你第二個問題
All right. I will ask you my second question.
你想當副總統嗎？
Do you want the  Vice Presidency for yourself?
這得看總統的意願，他是否…
I would serve at the pleasure  of the President. If that was his...
你提出這個建議  好讓自己取代馬修
You proposed this idea so that  you can take Matthews' place.
- 我沒那樣說  - 但是你想要的
-I did not say that.  -But it is what you want.
- 我要的是…  - 總統讓你當副手
-What I want is in the...  -The President makes you VP,
他讓你一起在2016年競選
he keeps you on the ticket in 2016,
你以此當作  2020年的競選跳板
and you use that as a  springboard to run in 2020.
告訴我  你心中不曾想過這種途徑
Tell me that trajectory  has never entered your mind.
琳達，我習慣
Well, Linda, I make a habit of
從任何假設情境  設想所有途徑
considering all trajectories  in any given situation.
但那是務實的做法  不是私人的做法
But that's a practical exercise,  not a personal one.
所以你拒絕承認
So you refuse to admit it.
承認那是我要的？  這根本不相干
Admit it's what I want? That's irrelevant.
是你要求開這場會議，不是我
You're the one who asked  for this meeting, not me.
這場會議是想要解決問題
This meeting's about  trying to solve a problem,
而不是滿足某種個人野心
not fulfill some personal ambition.
要是兩者都能達成  你也不會拒絕
But if both could be achieved,  you wouldn't object.
不管總統要誰去取代馬修
I think this is a sound course of action
我想這是很安全的行動路線
regardless ofwho the President  taps to replace Matthews.
我必須賭下目前擁有的一切
I must gamble everything I have right now.
我若老實說  她會拿來對付我
If I'm honest, she may use it against me.
如我不老實說  她不會採取行動
If I'm not, she won't lift a finger.
我自己也用這樣的策略
I've used this same tactic myself.
人一旦被攤在陽光下  就會任人宰割
Once someone is exposed,  they're at your mercy.
她要我這樣說
She wants to hear me say the words.
對
Yes.
我想當副總統
I want to be the Vice President.
我幫助你兒子進大學  希望你能有所回饋
And, yes, I helped your son get into college  in the hopes that you would return the favor.
然而我不能逼你這麼做
But I can't force you to do so, Linda.
但我認為我們  能組成令人畏懼的團隊
But I also think that  we would make a formidable team.
看看我們的成績
Look what we've been able to accomplish
就算處境艱困也有一番作為
even when we've been  at odds with each other.
想想如果我們不合作  能完成什麼
Now put your mind to what  we could accomplish if we weren't.
琳達，謝謝你的時間
Thank you for taking the time, Linda.
我再打給你，事情如何？
I'll call you back. How'd it go?
她不動聲色
She's holding her cards  very close to the chest.
- 有彼得的消息嗎？  - 沒有
-Any word from Peter?  -Nothing.
克裏絲汀娜說他躲在公寓
Christina said he wouldn't  leave the apartment.
我打給警衛室  他說彼得已經離開了
But I called the doorman,  and he said that Peter was gone.
- 去哪裏？  - 他不知道
-Where?  -He doesn't know.
他必須正式退出  才能對沃克施壓
He needs to officially withdraw  to put pressure on Walker.
我正試著找到他
I'm trying to track him down.
你怎麼一開始讓他跑了？
Why'd you let him  out of your sight in the first place?
我以為他在沖澡  他趁我和你講電話時溜掉
I thought he was showering. He disappeared  when I was on the phone with you.
道格，計劃原本是  他競選失利，然後退出
There was a plan here, Doug.  He explodes, he withdraws,
我們讓他再試一次  他悄悄引退
we put him back together,  and he quietly goes away.
自從媒體指控魯索  昨天早上接受匹茲堡
Russo has made no public appearances  since allegations that he was inebriated
WZPZ電台專訪時酒醉  他就神隱起來
during a radio interview  on WZPZ Pittsburgh yesterday morning.
民主黨領導群有些人建議
Sources among  the Democratic leadership have suggested
政黨目前考慮找人取代魯索
that the party is currently  considering options to replace Russo.
同時共和黨候選人  傑克史沃佛特的領先支持度
Meanwhile, Republican candidate  Jack Swofford's lead
根據CNN當夜選民民意調查
has jumped to a 24-point margin,
已經躍升到24個百分點
according to an overnight  CNN poll of registered voters.
史沃佛特的競選團隊  也提供一則勁爆消息
The Swofford campaign is also reporting  a sharp spike in contributions.
將近50萬元在過去20…
Nearly $500, 000 in the last 20...
魯索尚未出面，競選未定
我今早看到這個
I saw that this morning.
法蘭斯力推彼得競選
Francis got Peter to run.
你和他很熟嗎？
Do you know him well?
不熟
We weren't close.
你需要打電話嗎？  我可以到其他房間
Do you need to make calls?  'Cause I can head into the other room.
不必了，謝謝
I don't think so. Thanks.
去哪裏？
Where are you going?
到攝影棚，我今天應該去那裏
To the lab. I should've gone in today.
亞當
Adam.
- 亞當…  - 去吧，快去
-Adam...  -Just go. Go. Leave.
你覺得這可以維持多久？
How long do you think this  can possibly go on for?
我們不曾相處超過48小時
We have never spent more  than 48 hours together.
也許有理由這樣做
Maybe there's a reason for that.
我有部分仍愛著你
A part of me still loves you.
哪部分？
Which part?
克萊兒，我不能當急救站
I can't be just a pit stop, Claire,
- 或像是逃避…  - 別說了，你不只這樣
-or some sort of escape...  -Oh, come on. You're more than that.
或是彌補法蘭斯不足之處
Or a top-up on  whatever Francis can't provide.
閉嘴！亞當，他是我老公
Oh, fuck off! He's my husband, Adam.
我們經歷的事  遠比你能想像的還多
We've gone through more  than you could ever imagine.
我忌妒你的自由精神  深受吸引，不是人人都能這樣
I envy your free spirit, and I'm attracted to it,  but not all of us have that luxury.
克萊兒，所以我對你  才會這麼絕望
Which is what I find  so frustrating about you, Claire.
你做了選擇
You had a choice.
選擇不自由
You chose not to be free.
我選擇的是能讓我  愛超過一周的男人
No. What I chose was a man  I could love for more than a week.
我不該那麼說，我…
I shouldn't have said that. I...
至少你很誠實
At least you're being honest.
亞當，我無法像你一樣  只活在當下
I can't live moment to  moment like you, Adam.
我過去和法蘭斯在一起  也會和他共創未來
I have a history with Francis,  I have a future with him,
這比當下更長遠
and it's bigger than a moment.
那麼你該扼殺愛意
Then you should kill it.
不管你的哪一部分仍愛我
Whatever part of you still loves me.
如果你做不到
If you can't,
就由我來
I will.
- 亞當…  - 別說了
-Adam...  -No.
- 哪位？  - 甜心
-Hello?  -Hey. Hey, sweetie.
你好嗎？媽媽也在嗎？
How's it going? Are you with your mom?
她在樓下，要找她嗎？
She's downstairs.  You want me to go get her?
不用，我只是打來
No. No. I just wanted to call and say,
問你和弟弟好不好
you know, hey to your brother and you.
他在嗎？
Is he there?
我想他在他的房間裏
He's in his room, I think.
去叫他聽電話
Okay. You want to go get him?
等一下
Hold on.
他說不想和你說話
He says he doesn't want to talk to you.
- 為什麼？  - 爸，我們看了新聞
-Why not?  -We've seen the news, Dad.
昨天學校來了一大堆電視記者
There were all sorts of  TV cameras at our school yesterday.
媽要我們這周待在家裏
Mom's making us stay home this week.
我要你做件事，我要你
I want you to do something.  I want you to go to
到臥室的窗戶往外看
your bedroom window and look out.
有看到黑色的車嗎？
You see that black car?
- 有  - 那是我
-Yeah.  -That's me.
爸，你不該在那裏  媽會很生氣
You shouldn't be here, Dad.  Mom would be really angry.
我們不需要告訴她，對吧？
Well, we don't need to tell her. Right?
這只是…只是…
It'll just be... It'll just be...
只是我們的小秘密
It'll just be our little secret.
你的聲音聽起來好奇怪  像是在電台
Your voice sounds weird,  like it did on the radio.
你聽到了？
You heard that?
我有電腦
I have a computer.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
有時你老爸會犯錯
Sometimes your dad makes mistakes.
- 我得走了  - 不要
-I better go.  -No.
我不想聽你這樣的聲音
I don't like to hear  your voice when it's like this.
那聲音令我不好受，再見，爸
It makes me sad. Bye, Dad.
莎拉，拜託…
Sarah, please...
彼得？
Peter?
克裏絲汀娜
Christina.
你在哪裏？
Where are you?
我在…
I'm...
我不太好
I'm not doing so well.
彼得，你在哪裏？
Where are you, Peter?
- 我在車子裏  - 在開車嗎？
-I'm in my car.  -Are you driving?
沒有
No.
告訴我你在哪裏
Tell me where you are.
在孩子的家外面
I'm outside my kids' house.
- 麥德琳家？  - 對
-You mean Madeleine's?  -Yeah.
彼得，你待在哪裏，好嗎？
I need you to stay right there. Okay, Peter?
你會待在那裏嗎？
You'll stay there?
彼得
Peter.
彼得，你還在嗎？
Peter, are you still there?
喂？
Hello?
我想自首
I'd like to turn myself in.
為什麼？
For what?
幾個月前
A few months ago,
我因酒駕被警察攔檢
I was pulled over for drunk driving.
他們讓我離開，我應該有罪
They let me go. I should've been convicted.
先生，如果警察讓你走  我們現在不能逮捕你
Well, if you were let go, sir,  we can't arrest you for it now.
我酒駕來這裏  以這個罪名逮捕我
Well, I drunk drove here. Arrest me for that.
我們能送你到戒酒…
We can put you in a detox tank...
我要正式逮捕
I want to be formally arrested.
我是議員彼得魯索
My name is Congressman Peter Russo.
我一月在密西根大道被捕
I was arrested in January  on Michigan Avenue.
議員，請坐
Please have a seat, Congressman.
我得打幾通電話
I gotta make a few phone calls.
- 你找到他了嗎？  - 我在他前妻的家門前
-Have you found him?  -I'm in front of his ex-wife's house.
克裏絲汀娜說  他從那裏打電話
But Christina said he called from there.
- 他不在哪裏？  - 不在
-He's not there?  -No.
不過我在路邊發現他的電話
But his phone is. I found it by the curb.
我們沒辦法和他連絡？
So we have no way to contact him?
除非他要找我們
Not unless he reaches out to us.
- 這可不妙  - 要我報警嗎？
-This isn't good.  -Want me to alert the authorities?
再給他一點時間
Let's give him a little longer.
- 要多久？  - 大概六個月
-How long did it last?  -About six months.
- 他比較年長  - 大很多歲？
-He was older.  -A lot?
對
Yeah.
他是記者，還是在白宮工作？
Was he a journalist,  or did he work on the Hill?
我不方便說
I'd rather not say.
好吧
All right.
我曾經很愛慕他
He was someone I looked up to for a while.
為什麼分手？
Why did it end?
他有老婆
He has a wife.
我們知道遲早要結束
We both knew it was going to end eventually.
這真的…
I mean, it was really...
一團糟
It was fucked up.
我們第一次一起過夜時
The first night we spent together,
他說他會傷害我，然後拋棄我
he told me he was gonna  hurt me and then discard me.
當關係結束時  我說這兩件事都沒發生
And when it ended,  I told him that he'd done neither.
但是的確很傷
But it does hurt.
我不會傷害你
I won't hurt you.
你不能對我許這種諾言
Yeah, you can't promise me that.
我可以
Yes, I can.
- 有誰看到他嗎？  - 沒有
-Has anyone else seen him?  -No.
他獨自在偵訊室裏
He's in an interrogation room by himself.
我真不該蹚渾水
I never should've got mixed up  in this fucking mess.
邦尼，我們沒時間後悔
We're way behind regret time, Barney.
吩咐你的手下掩護他
Just have your guys keep him out of sight.
我需要後門
I'll need a back exit.
- 找到他了，謝謝  - 好
-I got him. Thanks.  -Yeah.
來
Come on.
彼得
Hey, Peter.
你的車呢？
Where's your car?
在街上
It's down the street.
我送你回家，你到我家  叫米契讓你進去
I'll drive you home. You go back to mine,  have Meechum let you in.
- 從這裏？  - 對
-This way?  -Yeah.
彼得，你到底在想什麼？
What were you thinking, Peter?
我需要為我的行動負責
I need to take responsibility for my actions.
讓自己入獄？
By getting yourself thrown in jail?
真正的責任
Real responsibility.
像他們在會議中說的實話
Like they talk about in the meetings,
而不是我們為競選說的謊言
not the lies we told for the campaign.
你剛剛的行為完全不顧後果
What you just did was extremely reckless.
我不在乎
I don't care.
法蘭，我明天要發表談話
I'm making a statement tomorrow, Frank.
關於退選？
About pulling out of the race?
這樣還不夠…
That's not enough. I...
我不要再躲藏
I need to stop hiding.
我們來一起想台詞
Well, let's work together on the language.
我得自己想，說出自己的話
I have to do it on my own.  It's gotta be in my own words.
彼得，這不再是  你一個人的事了吧？
Look, Peter, this isn't just  about you anymore, all right?
- 讓我幫你  - 我不要你幫
-Let me help you.  -I don't want your help.
當我被逮捕時  也不曾要求你幫我
I didn't ever ask your help  when I got arrested.
你的幫忙什麼時候幫過我？
When has your help ever helped me?
你可以照你想要的方式過生活
You can live your life the way you want to.
我不想再受人擺佈
I'm done being told how to live mine.
一定有可以不需要毀了一切
Well, there has to be  a way to take responsibility
才能負責任的方法
without shattering everything.
你願意至少討論一下嗎？
Are you at least willing  to have that discussion?
- 要我上樓嗎？  - 不要
-Do you want me to come upstairs?  -No.
彼得，我知道你很痛苦
I know you're in a lot of pain, Peter.
但是我不希望你今晚感到痛苦
But I don't want you to feel any pain tonight.
你可以有個嶄新的明天
Here. You can start fresh tomorrow.
說吧，我不會批判你  我甚至和你同一陣線
Go ahead. I won't judge you.  Hell, I'll even join you.
放鬆
Just relax.
現在到家了
You're home now.
不管你明天要面對什麼
Whatever it is you have to face tomorrow,
現在都不必面對
you don't have to face it now.
現在只有你和我
Right now, it's just you and me.
其餘的都不重要
The rest of the world doesn't matter.
你的孩子、克裏絲汀娜
Your children, Christina,
他們會原諒你
they will forgive you,
因為他們愛你，彼得
because you're loved, Peter.
毀了
Failed.
我毀了自己
I failed myself.
毀了我的家庭
I failed my family.
毀了競選
I failed the campaign.
彼得，沒那麼糟
No, you haven't, Peter.
我可以喝嗎？
May l?
我和克萊兒結婚時
You know,  when Claire and I were first married,
我們就談到生小孩的事
we talked about having children.
我很坦白地說  我不要任何小孩
I told her flat out I didn't want any.
雖然很自私卻很誠實
It was selfish but honest.
我的童年不快樂
I didn't have a particularly happy childhood.
我想你的童年也不快樂
I suspect you didn't either.
是不快樂
No.
看吧，人都會有痛苦
You see, no person avoids pain.
既然知道童年不快樂  就不需要讓孩子受苦
And I just didn't think it was right  to bring a child in knowing that.
現在回想起來，我…
But now when I think back, l...
明白那是懦弱
I realize that was cowardly.
我看到你
I see you,
想著，這是個勇敢的男人  比我勇敢多了
and I think, well, there's a brave man,  far braver than me.
我好害怕
I'm so tired.
當我想到…
When I think about...
我好累
I'm so tired.
你應該閉上眼睛
You should close your eyes.
讓事情過去
Let it all go.
我們有時間
We have all the time in the world.
彼得？
Peter?
彼得
Peter.
我走回來
I walked back.
不管接下幾小時發生什麼
Whatever happens in the next few hours,
不管你聽到什麼
whatever you hear,
我們都不談論
we will never speak of it.
議員…
Sir...
大概一個半鐘頭前  琳達告訴我
I heard from Linda about a half an hour ago.
總統要和你會面
The President wants to meet with you.
8點30分
8:30.
什麼事？
About what?
不知道
I don't know.
法蘭
Frank.
當你提出這個想法時  我並不認同
You know, when you brought up this idea,  I wasn't sold.
那讓我感到絕望和草率
It struck me as both desperate and careless.
但是琳達提出所有有利的一面
But then Linda laid out all the pros,
他們也小心評估不利的一面
and they clearly outweigh the cons.
我向吉姆解釋原因  希望他不會以為我瘋了
I explained our reasoning to Jim and hoped  he wouldn't think I was off my rocker.
我一開始是這麼認為  不過總統提出很棒的論政
I did at first, but the President  made some very good arguments.
法蘭，這是很大膽的一步  很高明
It's a bold move, Frank. I'm very impressed.
長官，謝謝你這麼願意接納建言
Well, thank you, sir,  for being open to the idea.
也謝謝總統先生願意冒風險
And thank you, Mr. President,  for taking the risk.
我們需要按部就班來實行
We'll need to work this out step-by-step.
- 必須完美執行  - 魯索呢？
-The execution has to be perfect.  -Where are things with Russo?
- 有他的消息嗎？  - 我們仍試圖在找他
-Any word from him yet?  -We're still trying to locate him.
- 有需要擔心的地方嗎？  - 已經兩天了
-Well, is there any cause for worry?  -It's been two days.
我得承認我有點擔心
I am a bit worried, I have to admit.
他這時候一定很難熬
I mean, this must be  an extremely difficult moment for him.
希望能快點找到他
We're hoping he'll reach out shortly.
我們派人找他  我要知道他人在哪裏
Let's get our people on it.  I want to know where he is.
現在只要他一退選  我們就得趕快行動
Now, once he withdraws,  we have to move quickly.
我們要如你提議的  發表聯合聲明
We'll make a joint statement,  as you proposed.
我想這是很清楚的訊息
It's a clear message, I think.
賓州對於我們很重要  我們不能棄守
Pennsylvanians matter to us,  and we're not gonna let them down.
沒錯，我認為吉姆  對白宮是很重要的資產
That's right. I'll say that Jim's  an invaluable asset to the White House,
但是我更欽佩他願意
but that I have great  admiration for the sacrifice
為了家鄉選民做犧牲
he's willing to make for  the people of his home state.
在他當選之前  你不該接受他辭職
And you should not accept his  resignation until he's elected.
這可顯示你對他的承諾不變
That will show  your continuing commitment to him.
這是很好的想法
I think that's a very good idea.
只要我能全身投入競選  我同意
As long as I can devote myself  wholly to the campaign, I agree.
要是吉姆贏了  就需要立刻提名副總統人選
Now, should Jim win, we'll need to  nominate a Vice President immediately.
琳達，你有人選嗎？
Linda, are you putting  together a list of names?
只要你縮小人選範圍  就可以啟動調查流程
Yes. And you can begin the vetting process  as soon as you narrow down the choices.
我已經有幾個最佳人選
I already have a short list of top contenders.
- 吉姆，我要聽聽你的意見  - 我很樂意
-I want your input on that, Jim.  -More than happy.
議員？
Congressman?
我們可以利用現有的基礎架構
We can use the existing infrastructure.
你同意奈許亞倫加入嗎？
Are you okay with Nash Aarons?
我喜歡奈許  不過我要引進一些自己的人馬
I like Nash, but I'll want to  bring in some of my own people.
沒問題，奈許很有團隊精神
Well, that won't be a problem.  Nash is a team player.
我們可以重新分配你現有  2016年競選連任資金…
And we can reallocate some of your  existing 2016 reelection funds...
抱歉，琳達
Excuse me. Linda.
彼得魯索死了
Peter Russo is dead.
自殺
Suicide.
他被發現人在車庫  車子未熄火
He was found in his garage  with the car still running.
法蘭，我很難過
I'm so sorry, Frank.
- 長官，我能獨處一下嗎？  - 當然
-May I have a moment, sir?  -Of course.
我會收集更多資料  開始起草聲明
I will get more information  and start drafting a statement.
我們重新安排時程  配合法蘭
Let's reschedule. Whenever is best for Frank.
法蘭斯  他們發現彼得今早
死於自家車庫，車子未熄火
議員彼得魯索  今早被發現死於車庫…
Congressman Peter Russo was found dead  early this morning in the parking garage...
我們怎麼沒報導這個？
Why didn't we break this?
美國特勤局發現他的屍體
U.S. Secret Service Agents  discovered his body after reports that
- 魯索從週六就失蹤  - 可惡！
-Russo had been missing since Saturday.  -Fuck!
他的屍體被移往  華府驗屍官辦公室
His body was transferred  to the D. C. Coroner's office
進行驗屍  確認他是死因是自殺
where an autopsy is expected  to confirm his death as a suicide.
出身費城的新進議員…
A junior congressman from Philadelphia...
- 享年36歲  - 喬伊，看這個
-Russo was 36 years old...  -Zoe. Look at this.
…育有兩名子女
...and is survived by two children.
- 我得到辦公室  - 魯索之前投入賓州州長
-I gotta get to the office.  -Russo was in the midst of a heated battle
競爭激烈的選戰中
for the governorship of Pennsylvania.
最後一次公開談話  是在匹茲堡WZPZ電台
He was last heard publicly during  a morning political radio show
晨間政論廣播節目
on Pittsburgh station WZPZ.
在專訪中，他口齒不清  態度恍神…
Now, during the interview, he slurred  his words, he sounded disoriented...
- 克裏絲汀娜  - …讓許多人相信
-Christina.  -...Ieading many to believe
- 他被換掉…  - 請幫我買回華府的火車票
-that he had relapsed...  -Can you get me a train back to D.C.?
本電視台為你播報關於  議員彼得魯索自殺
Right here on this TV station  for all your late-breaking details
這則重大新聞  所有最新的及時消息
about this major news story,  the suicide of Congressman Peter Russo.
接電話  回答我
他們發現彼得今早在車庫  車子未熄火
回家中
我現在難以表達感受
I find it very difficult to express  everything that I'm feeling right now,
我知道克萊兒有同樣的感覺
and I know Claire feels exactly the same.
彼得對我們來說非常特別
Peter was very special to us.
只要跟他接觸  所有人都會被他吸引
A sort of magnetic presence  that electrified everyone he touched.
我老公和我在過去幾個月裏  和他感情很好
And my husband and I became very  close to him in the past several months.
彼得不只是同事、朋友
Peter was more than a colleague,  more than a friend.
他是家人
He was family.
我們的心  和他的子女、母親同在
Our hearts go out to his children  and to his mother,
也和認識他的人  和他共事的人、愛他的人同在
to all of those who knew him  and worked with him and loved him.
希望大家尊重  他們的隱私和損失
We would ask that all of you respect  their privacy and honor their loss.
今天對於美國國會、對於賓州
Today is indeed a sad day  for the United States Congress,
還有我們所有人來說  是悲傷的一天
for the state of Pennsylvania,  and for all of us.
感謝大家
Thank you very much.